Guide to the John B. Snook Architectural Records Collection 1762-1948 PR 64
New-York Historical Society
John B. Snook architectural records collection
1762-1948
New-York Historical Society
PR 64
55.5 Linear feet in 60 boxes
The collection is comprised of ca. 2500 architectural drawings by John Butler Snook and his various firms.
Provenance
Gift of the estate of Thomas E. Snook, Jr., 1953.
Access Restrictions
Materials in this collection may be stored offsite. For more information on making arrangements to consult them, please visit www.nyhistory.org/library/visit.
Biographical Note
John Butler Snook (1815-1901) was born in England, and came to the United States as a child. His career as a practicing architect in New York City spanned nearly 60 years. He was educated as a carpenter, serving as an apprentice in his father's carpentry business, and was largely self-taught as an architect. In 1842 he joined the firm of Joseph Trench, and in less than five years he became the junior partner in the firm.
While associated with Trench, Snook designed the A. T. Stewart department store on lower Broadway, the first luxury dry-goods store in America, and the Metropolitan and St. Nicholas Hotels. After Trench moved west to San Francisco, Snook continued to work in New York City until the end of the century, focusing mainly on projects in the city, but also designing and constructing buildings in Brooklyn, the Bronx, Westchester County, and New Jersey.
Snook designed churches, hotels, residences, train depots, warehouses, tenements, and hospitals. While he did not specialize in one type of building, the majority of his work was in warehouses, commercial buildings, and tenements. In 1869, Cornelius Vanderbilt employed Snook to design the first Grand Central Depot, which was intended to serve as the main passenger terminal for the New York and Harlem Railroad and the New York Central and Hudson Railroad.
In 1836 Snook married Maria A. Weekes, with whom he had nine children that lived to adulthood. Three of these, James H., Samuel B., and Edward T., eventually joined his practice, which was renamed John B. Snook & Sons. One of Snook's sons-in-law, John W. Boylston, also worked in the firm. Snook died at his home in Brooklyn in 1901.
Chronology of Snook's Firms
1836-1840 Snook worked as a carpenter in partnership with William Beer, 328 Washington Street
1842-[1846] Snook worked for Joseph Trench and Company at 12 Chambers Street
[1846]-1857 Trench and Snook at 12 Chambers Street
1857-1887 John B. Snook at 12 Chambers Street
1887-1896 John B. Snook & Sons at 12 Chambers Street
1897-1901 John B. Snook & Sons at 261 Broadway
1901-[1969] John B. Snook Sons
Scope and Content Note
The John B. Snook Architectural Records Collection spans the period from 1762 to 1948 and contains architectural drawings, record books, and reference books from John Butler Snook and his descendents' careers as architects in New York City. The collection is divided into three series: Architectural Drawings, Record Books, and Printed Material from Snook's Library.
Arrangement
Architectural drawings were arranged by size and then given project numbers. Most drawings are rolled and stored in boxes but a few have been flattened and are stored in folders. Projects are listed by client name, if known, and then by project name and address.
Related Material at the New-York Historical Society
Additonal volumes from John B. Snook's library can be found in the New-York Historical Society's Library. Snook's trade sign from 1847 is held by the N-YHS Museum.
Separated Material
Additional volumes from John B. Snook's library can be found in the New-York Historical Society's Library. Snook's trade sign from 1847 is held by the N-YHS Museum.
Architectural drawings (visual works); Architecture -- United States -- 19th century -- Designs and plans.; Department stores; Tenement houses; Cast-iron fronts (Architecture); Architectural records.; Elevations (orthographic projections).; Architecture -- United States -- 20th century -- Designs and plans.; Blueprints (reprographic copies); A.T. Stewart & Co.; Hebrew Orphan Asylum of New York; John B. Snook & Sons; John B. Snook Sons; Trench & Snook; Trench, Joseph, 1810-1879
- Series I: Architectural Drawings, 1846-1948
  Scope and Contents note
  Series I. Architectural Drawings contains a total of 2,719 drawings representing 225 different projects. Drawings include elevations, plans, sections, mechanical and engineering drawings, blueprints, working drawings, and presentation drawings. The majority of the projects found here are buildings in New York City and surrounding boroughs and towns. Most projects represented are generally those from later in Snook's career. A few projects date from the time of John Snook Sons, the firm's name after Snook's death. Snook's design for the original Grand Central Terminal is only represented here by one large elevation, probably a presentation drawing.
  Projects are arranged by size of drawing, and are numbered accordingly for easy reference. The numbers were assigned by the N-YHS staff and do not reflect any intention on the part of the architect. All drawings for the same project are rolled together, unless some of the drawings required flat storage. A list of projects by geographical location, and by date, follow this finding aid.
  The architectural drawings were surveyed and inventoried in the summer of 2004. Those that could not be unrolled were humidified and flattened. Remaining rolled drawings are extremely fragile and may need conservation before being viewed. Please contact the Print Room staff at least one week before anticipated visit. Also, the collection was not processed per se, as there remains a great deal of research to be done on each building.
  - Henry Bergh Mausoleum Project #1, 1888 (Box 1)
  - St. James Church, Elberon, NJ Project #2, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Factory, Oakland, NJ Project #3, 1895 (Box 1)
  - 111 Cliff Street, New York, NY Project #4 (Box 1)
  - Robert James Livingston, Tablet inscription design and church auditorium, Hyde Park, NY Project #5 (Box 1)
  - Hebrew Orphan Asylum, Brooklyn, NY Project #6 (Box 1)
  - 419 East 58th Street, New York, NY Project #7 (Box 1)
  - Mrs. Jerome, Mrs (151) and Benjamin Blackledge (153), Tenements, 151-153 West 18th Street, New York NY Project #8, 1874 (Box 1)
  - 60-62 West 23rd Street, New York, NY Project #9, 1892 (Box 1)
  - 61-65 23rd Street, New York, NY Project #10 (Box 2)
  - 241-243 West 27th Street, New York, NY Project #11 (Box 2)
  - 131 West 38th Street, New York, NY Project #12 (Box 2)
  - 236 West 54th Street, New York, NY Project #13 (Box 2)
  - 57th Street, New York, NY Project #14 (Box 2)
  - Wendel Estate, Store and manufacturing, 151 Avenue C, New York, NY Project #15, 1894 (Box 2)
  - Fireproof doors, 157-159 Bank Street, New York, NY Project #16 (Box 2)
  - Barclay Street and College Place, New York, NY Project #17, 1895 (Box 2)
  - 356 Broadway, New York, NY Project #18, 1892 (Box 2)
  - Joseph F. Loubat Stores, 503-511 Broadway, New York, NY Project #19, 1878 (Box 3)
    General note
    See also: Folders 1-3
  - 632 Broadway, New York, NY Project #20, 1897 (Box 3)
  - 703-705 and 711 Broadway, New York, NY Project #21 (Box 3)
  - Chambers Street, New York, NY Project #22 (Box 3)
  - Chatham Street and Baxter Street, New York, NY Project #23 (Box 3)
  - Church Street and Walker Street, New York, NY Project #24 (Box 3)
  - Brill Brothers, Store, 47 Cortlandt Street, New York, NY Project #25 (Box 3)
  - Lewis, 78 Crosby Street, New York, NY Project #26, 1884 (Box 3)
  - Palmer, Store, 66-68 Duane Street, New York, NY Project #27, 1860 (Box 4)
  - Palmer, Store, 81-85 Duane Street, New York, NY Project #28 (Box 4)
  - David Korn, Tenement, 167 East Broadway, New York, NY Project #29, 1884 (Box 4)
  - Robert James Livingston, Store, 184 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY Project #30, 1873 (Box 4)
    See also: Folder 4
  - House, 240 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY Project #31 (Box 4)
  - Addition to Roof, 648-650 First Avenue, New York, NY Project #32 (Box 4)
  - 377-379 Fourth Avenue, New York, NY Project #33, 1876 (Box 5)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Arch No. 5, Frankfort Street, New York, NY Project #34 (Box 5)
  - 107-113 Franklin Street, New York, NY Project #35 (Box 5)
  - Greenwich Street and Chambers Street, New York, NY Project #36, 1877 (Box 5)
  - Hoffman, 110 John Street, New York, NY Project #37 (Box 5)
  - Apartment Building, Madison Avenue at 59th Street, New York, NY Project #38 (Box 5)
    See also: Oversize Folder 24
  - 200 Mercer Street, New York, NY Project #39 (Box 5)
  - Tenement, 244-246 Mulberry Street, New York, NY Project #40, 1885 (Box 5)
    See also: Folders 5-6
  - 108 Murray Street, New York, NY Project #41, 1894 (Box 6)
  - Elevator, 20 North William Street, New York, NY Project #42 (Box 6)
  - Roderick Green, Tenement, 64 Oliver Street, New York, NY Project #43, 1889 (Box 6)
    See also: Folder 7
  - 12 Peck Slip, New York, NY Project #44, 1880 (Box 6)
  - 22-26 Reade Street, New York, NY Project #45, 1916 (Box 6)
  - 207 Sullivan Street, New York, NY Project #46 (Box 6)
  - Tenth Avenue and 56th Street, New York, NY Project #47, 1887 (Box 6)
  - Office, 567 Third Avenue, New York, NY Project #48, 1908 (Box 6)
  - 50 Warren Street, New York, NY Project #49 (Box 6)
  - 20 Washington Street, New York, NY Project #50 (Box 7)
  - 65-67 Watt Street and 12-14 Desbrosses Street, New York, NY Project #51 (Box 7)
    See also: Folder 8
  - Chamberlain, Phelps & Co. Warehouse, West Street and Beach Street, New York, NY Project #52, 1867 (Box 7)
  - 80 West Street, New York, NY Project #53 (Box 7)
  - 188 William Street, New York, NY Project #54 (Box 7)
  - Offices, 79-81 Worth Street, New York, NY Project #55, 1944 (Box 7)
  - 177 West Street, New York, NY Project #56, 1891 (Box 7)
  - Bronx Gas & Electric Company, Westchester NY Project #57, 1900 (Box 7)
  - Lorillard Farm, Crow's Nest Mountain, Tuxedo Park, NY Project #58, 1898 (Box 7)
  - Factory, East Ridgewood [Queens], NY Project #59, 1917 (Box 8)
  - Cottage, Smithtown, NY Project #60, 1903 (Box 8)
  - Wendell Estate, Barn, Irvington, NY Project #61 (Box 8)
  - Wendell Estate, Iron Fence and Stone Wall, Irvington, NY Project #62 (Box 8)
  - Wendell Estate, Stables, Irvington, NY Project #63 (Box 8)
  - R. Alexander, Esq., Residence, New Rochelle, NY Project #64, 1924 (Box 8)
  - 124th Street and First Avenue, New York, NY Project #65 (Box 8)
  - 116 East 36th Street, New York, NY Project #66, 1895 (Box 8)
  - 553 East 135th Street, New York, NY Project #67, 1893 (Box 8)
  - Edward Higgins, Tenement, 610 East 150th Street, New York, NY Project #68, 1889 (Box 9)
  - Thomas F. Jeremiah, Tenements, 242-244 West 4th Street, New York, NY Project #69, 1884 (Box 9)
  - 113 West 22nd Street, New York, NY Project #70 (Box 9)
  - 226-228 West 27th Street, New York, NY Project #71 (Box 9)
  - 11 West 29th Street, New York, NY Project #72 (Box 9)
  - 304 West 38th Street, New York, NY Project #73, 1873 (Box 9)
  - Auto. Dynamic Company, 140 West 39th Street, New York, NY Project #74, 1898 (Box 9)
  - 41 West 51st Street, New York, NY Project #75, 1911 (Box 9)
  - Store and Tenement, 130-138 Attorney Street, New York, NY Project #76, 1891 (Box 9)
  - Bank Street at Thirteenth Avenue, New York, NY Project #77 (Box 9)
  - Patrick Skelly, Tenement, 167 Bleecker Street, New York, NY Project #78, 1886 (Box 10)
  - E.J. Gerry, 631-635 Broadway, New York, NY Project #79 (Box 10)
  - 734 Broadway, New York, NY Project #80, 1928 (Box 10)
  - Storm Estate, House, Broadway and Reade Street (SW corner), New York, NY Project #81, 1871 (Box 10)
    See also: Folder 9
  - D.W. Heidgard, Store, 272 Canal Street, New York, NY Project #82, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 307-311 Canal Street, New York, NY Project #83 (Box 10)
  - Spencer & Co. Stores, 329-331 Canal Street, New York, NY Project #84, 1883 (Box 10)
  - 365-367 Canal Street, New York, NY Project #85 (Box 11)
  - House, 211 Clinton Street, New York, NY Project #86 (Box 11)
  - Manhattan Pie Baking Company, Stables, 8 Columbia Street, New York, NY Project #87, 1889 (Box 11)
  - Store, 14 Duane Street, New York, NY Project #88, 1893 (Box 11)
  - 98 Duane Street, New York, NY Project #89 (Box 11)
  - Penthouse, Kips Bay, First Avenue and 37th Street, New York, NY Project #90 (Box 11)
  - Apartment Building, Flatbush Avenue and Hanson Pl., Brooklyn, NY Project #91 (Box 11)
  - 119-121 Forsythe Street, New York, NY Project #92 (Box 11)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Freezing and Cold Storage Company, Frankfort Street between Cliff Street and Pearl Street, New York, NY Project #93, 1897 (Box 11)
  - 11 Frankfort Street, New York, NY Project #94, 1897 (Box 11)
  - Thomas Morrell, Store, 207 Fulton Street, New York, NY Project #95, 1866 (Box 11)
  - 400 Grand Street, New York, NY Project #96 (Box 12)
  - Samuel B. Clark, Manufacturers, 496-498 Grand Street, New York, NY Project #97, 1889 (Box 12)
  - Herman Heidgard, Store, Grand Street and Elm Street, New York, NY Project #98, 1889 (Box 12)
    See also: Folder 10
  - Store and Tenement, Grand Street and Mott Street, New York, NY Project #99 (Box 12)
  - 14 Greene Street, New York, NY Project #100 (Box 12)
  - 120 Greene Street, New York, NY Project #101 (Box 12)
  - Jacob Korn, Tenements, Henry Street west of Clinton Street, New York, NY Project #102, 1874 (Box 12)
    See also: Folder 11
  - David Korn, Tenement, 198 Henry Street, New York, NY Project #103, 1884 (Box 12)
  - 138 Jane Street, New York, NY Project #104 (Box 12)
  - E.A. Hoffman & R. Hewitt, Manhattan Refrigeration Power Plant, Horatio Street, New York, NY Project #105, 1897 (Box 13)
  - 400 Hudson Street, New York, NY Project #106 (Box 13)
  - Elizabeth Brown, 52 James Street, New York, NY Project #107, 1899 (Box 13)
  - Skelly, Jay Street and Caroline Street, New York, NY Project #108, 1884 (Box 13)
  - 330 Lexington, New York, NY Project #109 (Box 13)
  - 112 Liberty Street, New York, NY Project #110 (Box 13)
  - Maiden Lane, Gold Street and Platt Street, New York, NY Project #111 (Box 13)
  - Charles Pfizer & Co., Store, 81 Maiden Lane, New York, NY Project #112, 1871 (Box 13)
  - Office, 119 Mulberry Street, New York, NY Project #113 (Box 13)
  - Ninth Avenue and Gansevoort Street, New York, NY Project #114, 1887 (Box 13)
  - 113 Park Row, New York, NY Project #115, [1893] (Box 14)
  - Daffey Brothers, Store, 439 Pearl Street, New York, NY Project #116 (Box 14)
  - South Street and Peck Slip, New York, NY Project #117, 1873 (Box 14)
  - John W. Hamersley, Store, 34 Pell Street, New York, NY Project #118, 1886 (Box 14)
  - Thomas Morrell, Store, 20 Reade Street, New York, NY Project #119, 1859 (Box 14)
  - Patrick Skelly, Tenement, 305 Spring Street, New York, NY Project #120, 1873 (Box 14)
  - Rutherford Stuyvesant, Tenement, 196-198 Third Avenue, New York, NY Project #121, 1886 (Box 14)
  - Addition of Stairs, 457-461 West Broadway, New York, NY Project #122 (Box 14)
  - John Bornholft, 88-90 Walker Street, New York, NY Project #123, 1884 (Box 15)
  - Bronx Gas & Electric Company, Westchester, NY Project #124, 1899 (Box 15)
  - C.F. Hoffman, Library Building, Charleston, SC Project #125, 1893 (Box 15)
  - Snook family Headstones, Greenwood Cemetery, Brooklyn, NY Project #126 (Box 15)
  - "Chestnuts," Residence, Bronx, NY Project #127 (Box 15)
  - Hebrew Orphan Asylum, Hospital, Brooklyn, NY Project #128 (Box 15)
  - New England Congregational Church, Brooklyn, NY Project #129, 1894 (Box 15)
  - R.J. Livingston, and E.T. Gerry, Mausoleum, NY Project #130 (Box 15)
  - Monquin Firehouse, West 38th Street and Seventh Avenue, New York, NY Project #131, 1886 (Box 15)
  - Inn, Newfoundland, NJ Project #132 (Box 16)
  - 53rd Street and Park Avenue, New York, NY Project #133, 1898 (Box 16)
  - Louis Rohdenburg, Apartments, 138th Street and Brook Avenue, Bronx, NY Project #134, 1892 (Box 16)
  - Charles Kneeland Estate, Tenement, 224 East 10th Street, New York, NY Project #135, 1897 (Box 16)
  - William H. Jackson, Offices, 31 East 17th Street, New York, NY Project #136, 1890 (Box 16)
  - 142 East 22nd Street, New York, NY Project #137, 1913 (Box 16)
  - 32 West 14th Street, New York, NY Project #138, 1895 (Box 16)
  - G. Rauchfuss, Tenement, 310 West 16th Street, New York, NY Project #139, 1872 (Box 16)
  - 237-243 West 27th Street, New York, NY Project #140, 1895 (Box 16, Folder unknown container)
  - O'Reilly, Skelly & Fogarty, 205 West 19th Street, New York, NY Project #141 (Box 17, Folder unknown container)
  - O'Reilly, Skelly & Fogarty, Tenement, 206 West 20th Street, New York, NY Project #142, 1878 (Box 17, Folder unknown container)
  - 41 West 28th Street, New York, NY Project #143, 1899 (Box 17, Folder unknown container)
  - Store, 9 West 29th Street, New York, NY Project #144 (Box 17, Folder unknown container)
  - 134-138 West 39th Street, New York, NY Project #145, 1900 (Box 17, Folder unknown container)
    See also: Folder 12
  - Bronx Gas and Electric Company, Avenue A between 8th Street and 9th Street, New York, NY Project #146 (Box 17, Folder unknown container)
  - 151-157 Bank Street, New York, NY Project #147 (Box 17, Folder unknown container)
  - George F. Morgan, Store and manufacturers, 159-161 Bank Street, New York, NY Project #148, 1892 (Box 17, Folder unknown container)
  - Bank Street and West Street, New York, NY Project #149 (Box 17, Folder unknown container)
    See also: Folder 13
  - Bethune Street and West Street, New York, NY Project #150, 1888 (Box 18, Folder unknown container)
  - Henry M Baker, Mary L. Baker, and others, Offices, stores, and loftsfor light manufacturing, 143 Bowery, New York, NY Project #151 (Box 18, Folder unknown container)
  - Bridge Street and Whitehall Street, New York, NY Project #152, 1900 (Box 18, Folder unknown container)
  - Lewis, 623 Broadway and 190 Mercer Street, New York, NY Project #153, 1881 (Box 18, Folder unknown container)
    See also: Folder 14
  - Jones & Company, 41 Broome Street, New York, NY Project #154, 1891 (Box 18, Folder unknown container)
  - 337-341 Canal Street and 7-9 Greene Street, New York, NY Project #155, 1868 (Box 18, Folder unknown container)
    See also: Oversize Folder 25
  - 113-115 Cedar Street, New York, NY Project #156, 1902 (Box 18, Folder unknown container)
  - 122 Chambers Street and 52 Warren Street, New York, NY Project #157 (Box 19, Folder unknown container)
  - Centre Street and Worth Street, New York, NY Project #158, 1889 (Box 19, Folder unknown container)
    See also: Folder 15
  - Levi A. Lockwood, Tenement, Christopher Street, New York, NY Project #159, 1878 (Box 19, Folder unknown container)
  - Jacob Korn, Tenement, 169 East Broadway, New York, NY Project #160, 1872 (Box 19, Folder unknown container)
  - Clarkson Street and Washington Street, New York, NY Project #161, 1890 (Box 19, Folder unknown container)
  - Office, Duane Street, New York, NY Project #162, 1890 (Box 19, Folder unknown container)
  - Office, 134-140 Duane Street, New York, NY Project #163 (Box 19, Folder unknown container)
  - Kips Bay Brewery, New York, NY Project #164, 1901 (Box 19, Folder unknown container)
  - 429 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY Project #165, after 1891 (Box 20, Folder unknown container)
  - 55 Maiden Lane, New York, NY Project #166 (Box 20, Folder unknown container)
  - John T. Williams, Stores, 152-154 Franklin, New York, NY Project #167, 1890 (Box 20, Folder unknown container)
  - S. B. Clark & Son, 494 Grand Street, New York, NY Project #168 (Box 20, Folder unknown container)
  - 50-54 Greenwich Street, New York, NY Project #169, 1894 (Box 20, Folder unknown container)
  - Mason, House, 227 Greenwich Street, New York, NY Project #170, 1894-1895 (Box 20, Folder unknown container)
  - Hugh O'Reilly, Store, Hudson Street and Houston Street, New York, NY Project #171, 1869 (Box 20, Folder unknown container)
  - 95-99 Hudson Street, New York, NY Project #172, 1890 (Box 20, Folder unknown container)
  - Ann Brown, Tenement, 48-50 James Street, New York, NY Project #173, 1899-1901 (Box 21, Folder unknown container)
  - 4 Staple Street, New York, NY Project #174, 1900 (Box 21, Folder unknown container)
  - Louis T. Williams, Offices, Laight Street and Varick Street, New York, NY Project #175, 1890 (Box 21, Folder unknown container)
  - 79-81 Leonard Street, New York, NY Project #176 (Box 21, Folder unknown container)
  - 734 Lexington, New York, NY Project #177 (Box 12, Folder unknown container)
  - 5-7 Maiden Lane, New York, NY Project #178, 1899 (Box 21, Folder unknown container)
  - 219-249 McKibben Street, Brooklyn, NY Project #179, 1898 (Box 21, Folder unknown container)
  - Apartment/Rooming Houses, 51 Washington Square South, New York, NY Project #180 (Box 22, Folder unknown container)
  - Mrs. Carrie Gans, Stores, 151 Spring Street, New York, NY Project #181, 1889 (Box 22, Folder unknown container)
  - Lewis, 31-33 Mercer Street, New York, NY Project #182 (Box 22, Folder unknown container)
    See also: Folder 16
  - Moore Street and West Street, New York, NY Project #183, 1878 (Box 22, Folder unknown container)
  - Edward Horton, Tenement, 95 Ninth Avenue, New York, NY Project #184, 1874 (Box 22, Folder unknown container)
  - G. Rauchfuss, Tenement, 195 Prince Street, New York, NY Project #185, 1879 (Box 22, Folder unknown container)
  - Adolph Pfender, Esq., Store, 18 Reade Street, New York, NY Project #186, 1859 (Box 22, Folder unknown container)
    See also: Folder 17
  - Hotel[?], Sixth Avenue and 38th Street, New York, NY Project #187 (Box 22, Folder unknown container)
  - Bronx Gas & Electric Company, Westchester, NY Project #188, 1898 (Box 23, Folder unknown container)
  - Bronx Gas & Electric Company, Westchester, NY Project #189, 1894 (Box 23, Folder unknown container)
  - Jacob Lorrilard, House, 135-155 South Fifth Avenue, New York, NY Project #190, 1899 (Box 23, Folder unknown container)
  - Dwelling, Third Avenue between 65th Street and 66th Street, New York, NY Project #191 (Box 23, Folder unknown container)
  - Heipershausen Brothers, Boiler Shop, 49-51 Tompkins Street, New York, NY Project #192, 1899 (Box 23, Folder unknown container)
  - 60-62 Warren Street, New York, NY Project #193 (Box 23, Folder unknown container)
  - John Ridley Estate, Store, 522 Washington Street, New York, NY Project #194, 1893 (Box 23, Folder unknown container)
  - Spring Street and Hudson Street, New York, NY Project #195, 1894 (Box 24-25, Folder unknown container)
  - 20 West 14th Street, New York, NY Project #196 (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - Nicholas Brown, Tenement, 44-46 Madison Avenue, New York, NY Project #197, 1901 (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - Mill, East 48th Street and East River, New York, NY Project #198 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - Lydia Hoyt Estate, Offices, 40-44 Pine Street, New York, NY Project #199, 1891 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - Store and Tenement, Tenth Avenue and 17th Street, New York, NY Project #200, 1898 (Box 28, Folder unknown container)
  - Bronx Gas & Electric Company, Main Street and Second Street, Westchester, NY Project #201 (Box 28, Folder unknown container)
  - 20-24 20th Street, New York, NY Project #202 (Box 29, Folder unknown container)
  - P.R. Weiler, Stores, Center Street and Walker Street, New York, NY Project #203, 1883 (Box 30, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank G. Belsito, Tenement, Carroll Street and Denton Place, Brooklyn, NY Project #204 (Box 31, Folder unknown container)
  - Cold Storage Warehouse, Jersey City, NJ Project #205 (Box 31, Folder unknown container)
  - Madison Avenue and 59th Street, New York, NY Project #206 (Box 32, Folder unknown container)
  - Hoffman, Mercantile Building, 105-107 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY Project #207 (Box 33, Folder unknown container)